ACTWU's Organizing Department Records. 5619/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Sam Fox Retirement Dinner, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  March 22 nd. Prince Hotel
- Canadian Conference, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  September 22-25th. Niagara Falls, Ontario, Canada
- Canadian Conference, 1981-1983 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  May 8-11th. Quebec City
- Canadian Staff Conference, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  August. Gananoque, Ontario
- Canada Staff Meeting, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  Toronto Canada
- Canadian Staff, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  June 25th
- 2nd Biennial Canadian Conference, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 22)
- Canadian Conferences. Speeches by Sol Stetin, 1971-1979 (Box 74, Folder 23)
- Canadian Conference, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  Scott Hoyman's File. English and French
- Canadian Conference, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  June 18-20th
- Canadian Staff Conference, 1981-1983 (Box 74, Folder 26)
- Winnipeg Joint Council, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 27)
- Southern Textile Reg. General, 1983-1986 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Southern Textile Region Joint Board, 1983-1985 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  Constitution and Charter
- Southern Textile Regional Joint Board Meeting., 1983-1985 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Southern Textile Mills. Changes in Ownership, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  ACTWU Research Dept
- Sheeting, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Towels (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Concord Plants (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Washcloth (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Pillowcase (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Southern Organizing, 1984-1986 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Southern Textile Region. Bruce Raynor, 1986-1987 (Box 75, Folder 11)
- Southern Textile Region. Jim Walraven, 1981-1985 (Box 75, Folder 12)
- Southern Textile Regional Joint Board, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 13)
- Southern Textile Region, 1984-1986 (Box 75, Folder 14)
- Bi-Country Joint Board. Carlton Rakes and Sidney Young, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 15)
- Southern. Bi-county and Northern North Carolina, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 16)
- Southern. Bi. County and Northern N. Carolina, 1983-1986 (Box 75, Folder 17)
- Bi County and Northern North Carolina, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 18)
- Central North Carolina Joint Board, 1984-1986 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  Henry Mann
- Central North Carolina, 1985-1986 (Box 75, Folder 20)
- Central North Carolina Joint Board, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 21)
- Central North Carolina Joint Board, 1986 (Box 75, Folder 22)
- Southern. Central Alabama- Georgia Joint Board, 1984-1986 (Box 75, Folder 23)
- Southern. Central Alabama- Georgia Joint Board Joe Suarez, 1986 (Box 75, Folder 24)
- Southern. G.T.A. Area Joint Board, 1984-1986 (Box 75, Folder 25)
- Southern. Memphis Area Joint Board, 1984-1985 (Box 75, Folder 26)
- Southern Roanoke Vally Joint Board, 1984-1985 (Box 75, Folder 27)
- Roanoke Valley Joint Board, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 28)
- Southern Roanoke Valley Joint Board Clyde Bush, 1984-1987 (Box 75, Folder 29)
- Southern S. C. Coastal Joint Board. James Johnson, 1984-1986 (Box 75, Folder 30)
- Southern South Carolina Joint Board, 1985-1986 (Box 75, Folder 31)
- Southern. Western Carolinas Joint Board, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 32)
- Western, 1983-1984 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  Frank Nicholas, Jr
- Western. Western Region, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 34)
- Western Region, 1978-1983 (Box 75, Folder 35)
  formerly West Coast Region Joint Board.
- Western Organizing, 1980-1982 (Box 75, Folder 36)
- Western Personnel, 1981-1982 (Box 75, Folder 37)
- Western California Joint Board, 1981-1986 (Box 75, Folder 38)
- Western California Joint Board Action, 1982-1986 (Box 75, Folder 39)
- Western Pacific North West Joint Board, 1980-1987 (Box 75, Folder 40)
- Far West-LA Joint Board. Merger into CA. Joint Board, 1977-1983 (Box 75, Folder 41)
- West Coast. Hygeia Materials, 1974-1981 (Box 75, Folder 42)
- Frank Nicholas, 1972-1979 (Box 75, Folder 43)
- John Alleruzzo. Canadian Director, 1986-1987 (Box 75, Folder 44)
- Canada. Co Director: Charles (Bud) Clark and Sam Fox, 1977-1986 (Box 75, Folder 45)
- Canadian Clippings, 1978-1984 (Box 75, Folder 46)
- Canada. Education Dept., 1981-1984 (Box 75, Folder 47)
- Canadian STRIKE authorization letter, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 48)
- Canada. Time Study Problem, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 49)
- Canada Organizing, 1976-1986 (Box 75, Folder 50)
- Canada Personnel, 1979-1986 (Box 75, Folder 51)
- Canada Legal Fees, 1977-1984 (Box 75, Folder 52)
- Canadian Labor Congress, 1976-1986 (Box 75, Folder 53)
- Canada. New Democratic Party of Ontario, 1976-1983 (Box 75, Folder 54)
- Canada Greater Cornwall Joint Board, 1978-1987 (Box 75, Folder 55)
- Greater Cornwall Joint Board, 1979-1983 (Box 75, Folder 56)
- Maine Joint Board, 1982-1987 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Maine Joint Board ACTWU Audit Report, 1983-1986 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- New England Maine Joint Board, 1983-1987 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Bates Fabrics, 1977-1987 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- New England Maine Joint Board, 1982-1983 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- New England. Maine Joint Board, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- New England. Maine Joint Board By-Laws, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- N. E. Biddeford-Saco Joint Board, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- N. E. Greater North Eastern Joint Board., 1983-1987 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Greater Northeastern Joint Board, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Merger Papers. Greater N.E. Joint Board, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Granite State Joint Board, 1979-1980 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  Manchester, N.H.
- W. S. Libbey Co., 1980-1986 (Box 76, Folder 13)
- ACTWU, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 14)
- W. S. Libbey. Negotiations, Proposals, and Contracts, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 15)
- W. S. Libbey Co. NLRB-Decert; ULP; UC, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 16)
- W. S. Libbey. Safety and Health, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 17)
- Maine Department of Labor Documents, 1983-1986 (Box 76, Folder 18)
- Negotiations- Proposals, notes, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 19)
- News Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 76, Folder 20)
- Basic Research, Documents, ect., 1985-1986 (Box 76, Folder 21)
- Contracts- Bargaining Info, 1985-1986 (Box 76, Folder 22)
- Greater Northeastern Joint Board, 1983-1987 (Box 76, Folder 23)
- Merger Materials, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 24)
- Boott Hydro- Decertification, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 25)
- Boott Hydro Negotiations, 1986-1987 (Box 76, Folder 26)
- Boott Mills Negotiations, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 27)
- Monthly Cash and Report Sheet, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 28)
- Greater N. Eastern Joint Board, 1985-1987 (Box 76, Folder 29)
- N. E. General, 1978-1986 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- N. E. Southern New England Joint Board, 1984-1987 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Southern N. E. Joint Board By Laws, 1978-1984 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- N. E. Southern Joint Board, 1982-1983 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Fall River Joint Board Merged with Southern N.E., 1981-1982 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- New Bedford Joint Board Merger agreement with N.E. Regional Joint Board, 1979-1982 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- N. E. Regional Joint Board and New Bedford area, 1985-1986 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Setting Piece Rates. A Training Manual for Union Members, 1983 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- N. E. Organizing, 1982-1985 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- New England Misc., 1986-1987 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- N. E. Organizing Misc., 1985-1986 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- N. E. Organizing List from Frank Myers, 1984-1985 (Box 77, Folder 12)
- N. E. Organizing Telephone Poll Probe, 1984-1985 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- N. E. Coordinated Organizing Program, 1979-1982 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- N. E. Organizing Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 77, Folder 15)
- N. E. Staff Meeting, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  January 25th. Malbora, Mass
- N. E. Survey Report, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 17)
- N. E. Organizing Project, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 18)
- Mid Atlantic Reg. Joint Board, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Mid Atlantic Region, 1983-1986 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Mid-Atlantic Organizing, 1984-1986 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Mid Atlantic Personnel, 1980-1986 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Mid-Atlantic. Contract Settlements, 1982-1986 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Pennsylvania Tri-State Joint Board, 1982-1983 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Mid-Atlantic. Dernoncourt Scholarship, 1982-1983 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Mid-Atlantic. Diane Dunton Scholarship, 1983-1984 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Mid-Atlantic. Region and Synthetics Division, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Mid Atlantic Regional Fall Conference, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  October 24-25th
- Mid Atlantic. The Agitator, 1983-1985 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Mid Atlantic Regional Joint Board Constitution and Charter, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Mid-Atlantic Reg. Joint Board Organizational Papers, 1983-1984 (Box 78, Folder 13)
- Mid-Atlantic. Carlisle Area Office, 1982-1987 (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Mid-Atlantic. Fredericksburg Area, 1985-1986 (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Mid-Atlantic. Philadelphia Area., 1982-1986 (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Mid-Atlantic. Phillipsburg Area Office, 1983-1985 (Box 78, Folder 18)
- Local # 6. Lewistown, Pennsylvania, 1969-1982 (Box 78, Folder 19)
- Mid-Atlantic. Local 9, 1977-1986 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  Parkersburg, West Virginia
- Quin State. Mid Atlantic. Local # 10, 1977-1985 (Box 78, Folder 21)
- Mid-Atlantic. Local # 10, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  Marcus Hook, Pennsylvania
- Local # 10. Problem and Audit, 1975-1978 (Box 78, Folder 23)
- Mid-Atlantic Region. Philadelphia - Local 80, 1985-1986 (Box 78, Folder 24)
- Mid-Atlantic Local 371-T, 1979-1986 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  Front Royal, Virginia
- Mid-Atlantic Region. Local 713, 1984-1985 (Box 78, Folder 26)
- Mid-Atlantic. Local 1034, 1980-1985 (Box 78, Folder 27)
- Mid-Atlantic. Local 1071, 1984-1986 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  Altoona, Pennsylvania
- Mid-Atlantic. Local 1700, 1973-1980 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  Bloomsburg, Pennsylvania
- Mid-Atlantic. Local 1853, 1972-1980 (Box 78, Folder 30)
- Mid-Atlantic. Local 1874, 1976-1984 (Box 78, Folder 31)
  Cumberland, Maryland
- Mid-Atlantic. Various Locals, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 32)
- Mid Atlantic Region. Request for Reinstatement of Local, 1985-1986 (Box 78, Folder 33)
- Mid Atlantic Regional Joint Board, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 34)
  March 7 - 9th. Carlisle, Pennsylvania. Embers Motel
- Mid-Atlantic Regional Conference, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 35)
  August 16th, Blacksburg, Virginia
- Mid Atlantic. Region/Synthetic. Conferences and Dinner, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 36)
  March 9-10th. Washington D.C.
- Mid-Atlantic Regional Joint Board, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 38)
  November 9th. Philadelphia
- Mid-Atlantic Textile Region-Staff. Training Planning Session, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 39)
  Aug 28th. Meany Center
- Mid Atlantic Education Planning Session. Meeting with Larry Rogin, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 40)
  August 3rd. Washington DC
- Mid-Atlantic Regional Joint Board Conference, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 42)
  October 28-30th
- Upper South and Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 43)
  June 15th. Washington DC
- Quin State Staff Mtg., 1982-1983 (Box 78, Folder 44)
  March 16-18th. Mt. Pocono, Pennsylvania.
- Quin State Region Staff Mtg. Documents, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 45)
  March 16-18th
- Upper South Regional Conference and Synthetics Division Conference, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 46)
  March 13th. Meany Labor Center
- Mid-Atlantic Region- Tour of Eastern PA., 1983 (Box 78, Folder 47)
  January 10-13th
- Upper South Regional Joint Board Mtg., 1982 (Box 78, Folder 48)
- Pennsylvania Textile Division, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 49)
- Upper South Regional Joint Board Mtg., 1982 (Box 78, Folder 50)
  February 27th
- Quin State and N. Y. Meetings, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 51)
  February 17-20th
- Upper South Regional Mtg., 1981 (Box 78, Folder 53)
  April 5th
- NY/NJ Region. Murray Moreno, 1983-1986 (Box 78, Folder 54)
- NY/NJ Greater New York Joint Board, 1939-1982 (Box 78, Folder 56)
- NY/NJ Regional General/Misc, 1983-1984 (Box 78, Folder 57)
- NY/NJ Organizing, 1983-1985 (Box 78, Folder 58)
- Buffalo Misc. Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 78, Folder 59)
- Buffalo Joint Board, 1982-1985 (Box 78, Folder 60)
  Betty Milerski versus Bernel Foan
- NY/NJ Central and South Jersey Joint Board, 1976-1986 (Box 78, Folder 61)
- Meeting with Central and South Jersey Joint Board, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 62)
- NY/NJ Greater Northern Textile Joint Board, 1981-1987 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Great Northern Joint Board. Administrationship File, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- NY/NJ Greater Northern Textile Joint Board, 1980-1981 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Hudson Valley Audits [folder 1 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Hudson Valley Audits [folder 2 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Hudson Valley Joint Board, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- Hudson Valley Area Joint Board Welfare Fund, 1985-1987 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- Hudson Valley Area Joint Board Proposal Agreement, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- Hudson Valley Joint Board Proposed Merger with Capital District Joint Board, 1976-1980 (Box 79, Folder 13)
- NY/NJ Hudson Valley Area Joint Board, 1982-1983 (Box 79, Folder 14)
- Maps. Hudson Valley Joint Board, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 15)
- Hudson Valley Area Joint Board, 1979-1983 (Box 79, Folder 16)
- Hudson Valley Area. Joint Board By - Laws, 1976 (Box 79, Folder 17)
- Merger of Amsterdam Joint Board With Hudson Valley Joint Board, 1974-1976 (Box 79, Folder 18)
- Greater Northern Textile Joint Board, 1968-1977 (Box 79, Folder 19)
- Utica Joint Board., 1970-1977 (Box 79, Folder 20)
- NY/NJ. North Jersey Joint Board., 1975-1987 (Box 79, Folder 21)
- Dillon/Israel Bond Dinner, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 22)
- Local 701-T, 1981-1985 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  Fulton, NY
- NY/NJ Local 1085, 1979-1983 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  Auburn, NY
- Johnson and Johnson. TWUA 1st Contract. Local 630., 1944-1985 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  May 15th
- Local 630. Executive Board. Mtg., 1986 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  February 11th. New Brunswick, NJ
- NY/NJ Local # 630, 1979-1985 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  New Brunswick, NJ
- Local 630. Installation, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  March 19th
- Johnson and Johnson. Local 630. Meeting with Albuquerque, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 29)
- Local # 3 Greater Northern Joint Board, 1977-1982 (Box 79, Folder 30)
- NY/NJ Local 1733, 1981-1986 (Box 79, Folder 31)
- Local 1733. Lists Executive Board., 1980 (Box 79, Folder 32)
- Local 1733 By-Laws Amendments and Constitution, 1979-1982 (Box 79, Folder 33)
- ACTWU Pensioners, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 34)
- Local 1733. Dye Problem, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 35)
- 1935 Book. Local 1733. "What Dye Workers have won", 1987 (Box 79, Folder 37)
- NY/NJ Local 1932, 1980-1986 (Box 79, Folder 38)
- NY/NJ Local 2052 By-Laws and Amendments, 1971-1975 (Box 79, Folder 40)
- NY/NJ Meeting, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 41)
- ACTWU. NY/NJ Leadership Mtg., 1984 (Box 79, Folder 42)
  May 29th
- Quin State Dyers Safety Conference, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 43)
- OSHA Mtg. of Quin State Div., 1981 (Box 79, Folder 44)
- Local 7587, 1980-1982 (Box 79, Folder 45)
- NY/NJ. Master Weavers. Local 7587, 1971-1979 (Box 79, Folder 47)
- ACTWU By-Laws, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 48)
- Local 189T. Bemis Company, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Mid-West. St. Louis Joint Board By- Laws, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Mid-West. St. Louis Joint Board Mortgage Burning., 1978 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  August 8th
- Mid-West. St. Louis. Joint Board Building Loan, 1966-1978 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- St. Louis Joint Board Meeting, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Local 2440. Duluth Community Action Program, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Mid-West. Twin City Joint Board, 1985-1987 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Mid-West. Financial Data and Audit. Twin City Joint Board, 1980-1981 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- Mid-West Chicago Joint Board Superseniority and Dues Rebate Questions, 1983 (Box 80, Folder 17)
- Synthetics Div. Local 482, 1982-1983 (Box 80, Folder 18)
- Mid-West Region. Local 487, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 19)
- Mid-West Local # 748, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  Houston, Texas
- Mid-West. Local # 1374, 1979-1983 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  Herrin, Illinois
- Mid-West Local 1703. LM3 Report, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 22)
- Mid-West Local # 1771, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 24)
- Mid-West Chicago Joint Board Local 1871, 1983 (Box 80, Folder 26)
  Brodhead, Wisconsin
- Midwest- Staff Meeting, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  February
- Midwest Conference and Bag & Packaging Conference, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 31)
  June 3-6th. Springfield, Illinois
- Mid-West Conference and Bag & Packaging, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 32)
  October 4-7th
- Mid-West Conference and Bag & Packaging, 1983 (Box 80, Folder 33)
- Mid-West Staff Mtg., 1983 (Box 80, Folder 34)
  August 12th. Chicago, Illinois
- S. Hoyman, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 35)
  June 18-19th. Chicago
- Mid-West Regional Conference, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 36)
- Mid-West Staff Mtg., 1981 (Box 80, Folder 37)
- Mid-West Bag and Packaging Conference, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 39)
  Indianapolis, Indiana
- South Regional Joint Board By-Laws, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 43)
- Mid-South Regional Board. By-Laws, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 45)
  December 5th
- South Regional Joint Board, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 46)
  Myrtle Beach, South Carolina
- Central North Carolina Joint Board, 1980-1982 (Box 80, Folder 47)
- Misc. ACTWU Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 80, Folder 49)
- Central North Carolina Joint Board By-Laws, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 50)
- By-Laws of the Bi Country and Northern North Carolina Joint Board, 1977 (Box 80, Folder 52)
- Bi-County By- Laws, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 53)
- Bassett- Walker,Inc., 1982 (Box 80, Folder 54)
- Southern Bi-County and Northern N. C. Joint Board, 1981-1982 (Box 80, Folder 55)
- Bi County Joint Board Real Property, 1956-1986 (Box 80, Folder 56)
- ACTWU, 1978-1983 (Box 80, Folder 57)
- Southern Clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 80, Folder 58)
- Southern. Historical Structure and Background, 1970-1977 (Box 80, Folder 59)
- JPS. Roanoke Plant. Chemical Hazards, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 60)
- ACTWU Correspondence and Documents, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- ACTWU Correspondence and Documents, 1982-1983 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- ACTWU Correspondence and Constitution, 1980-1981 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Constitution. Roanoke Valley Joint Board, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Southern New Orleans Joint Board, 1980-1982 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Correspondence and Documents, 1981-1982 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- GTA, 1978-19812 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- Memphis Joint Board Best Manufacturing, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Southern Wage Agitation, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Southern Formerly Revolving Fund Charlotte Office, 1980-1983 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- South Carolina Union Information, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 13)
- Southern Elections, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 14)
- Southern- J. Sheinkman, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 16)
- Southern. Cotton Dust, 1980-1981 (Box 81, Folder 17)
- Bob Freeman Correspondence, 1962-1982 (Box 81, Folder 18)
- Financial Data. Pacific Northwest Joint Board, 1977-1981 (Box 81, Folder 19)
- Financial Data. Unaffiliated Locals, 1981-1983 (Box 81, Folder 20)
- Financial Data. Unaffiliated Locals, 1978-1980 (Box 81, Folder 21)
- ACTWU Resources, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 22)
- Financial Data. St. Louis Joint Board, 1981-1983 (Box 81, Folder 23)
- Financial Data. Southern New England Joint Board, 1982-1984 (Box 81, Folder 25)
- Monthly Cash and Report Sheet, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 26)
- Southern Textile Region Joint Board Financial Data, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 29)
- Southwestern Ontario Textile Joint Board, 1979-1984 (Box 81, Folder 30)
- Philadelphia Joint Board (Box 81, Folder 33)
- Financial Data. Quebec Joint Board, 1977-1981 (Box 81, Folder 34)
- Financial Reports., 1976-1983 (Box 81, Folder 37)
- Joint Board Financial Data. Half Yearly Summary of Activity, 1983-1986 (Box 81, Folder 38)
- Joint Board. Financial Data, 1978-1979 (Box 81, Folder 39)
- Merger of Joint Boards and Unaffiliated Locals to Joint Boards, 1977-1978 (Box 81, Folder 40)
- Financial Data. Central Alabama/ Georgia Joint Board, 1977-1984 (Box 81, Folder 43)
- Financial Data. Central North Carolina Joint Board, 1977 (Box 81, Folder 44)
- Financial Data Chicago Joint Board, 1980-1982 (Box 81, Folder 45)
- Cincinnati Joint Board Financial Data, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 47)
- Financial Data. Cone Council, 1980-1984 (Box 81, Folder 48)
- Financial Data. Western Carolinas Joint Board, 1980-1983 (Box 81, Folder 49)
- Financial Data. G.T.A. Joint Board, 1979-1982 (Box 81, Folder 50)
- Financial Data. Greater Cornwall Joint Board, 1977-1979 (Box 81, Folder 51)
- Financial Data. Greater Fall River Joint Board, 1977-1980 (Box 81, Folder 52)
- Financial Data. Greater New York Joint Board, 1977-1982 (Box 81, Folder 53)
- Financial Data. Northeastern Mass. Joint Board, 1979-1985 (Box 81, Folder 54)
- Financial Data. Granite State Joint Board, 1977-1981 (Box 81, Folder 55)
- Financial Data. Greater Northern Textile Joint Board, 1981-1983 (Box 81, Folder 56)
- Financial Data. Greater Northern Joint Board, 1973-1981 (Box 81, Folder 57)
- Financial Data. Greater Toronto Joint Board, 1977-1982 (Box 81, Folder 58)
- Financial Data. Indiana/ Kentucky Joint Board, 1981-1983 (Box 81, Folder 59)
- Financial Data. Kansas City Joint Board, 1977-1982 (Box 81, Folder 60)
- Financial Data. Maine Joint Board, 1977-1984 (Box 81, Folder 61)
- Financial Data. Memphis Area Joint Board, 1979-1982 (Box 81, Folder 62)
- Financial Data. Delaware Valley Joint Board, 1979-1982 (Box 81, Folder 63)
- Financial Data. Delaware Valley Joint Board, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 64)
- Financial Data. Garden Spot Joint Board, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 65)
- Financial Data. Garden Spot Joint Board, 1979-1982 (Box 81, Folder 66)
- Monthly Cash and Report Sheet. Mid-Atlantic Regional., 1984 (Box 81, Folder 67)
- Financial Data. Philadelphia Textile Workers Joint Board, 1977-1983 (Box 81, Folder 68)
- Financial Data. Schuylkill Valley District, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 69)
- Financial Data. Schuylkill Valley District Joint Board, 1979-1982 (Box 81, Folder 70)
- Financial Data. Mid-Atlantic, 1979-1981 (Box 81, Folder 71)
- Financial Data. Mid-Atlantic, 1981-1983 (Box 81, Folder 72)
- Financial Data. New Bedford Joint Board, 1977-1981 (Box 81, Folder 73)
- Financial Data. New Orleans Joint Board, 1977-1981 (Box 81, Folder 74)
- Financial Data. North Jersey Joint Board, 1979-1982 (Box 81, Folder 75)
- Financial Data. Ohio State Joint Board, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 76)
- Financial Data. Ohio State Joint Board, 1977-1981 (Box 81, Folder 77)
- Financial Data. Twin City Joint Board, 1979-1981 (Box 81, Folder 78)
- Financial Data. Central and South Jersey Joint Board, 1979-1983 (Box 81, Folder 79)
- United Textile Workers, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- J. & J.. Incentive Task Force, 1977-1983 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- J. & J.. IUD Collective Bargaining, 1977-1980 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- J. & J., 1982 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- J. & J.. Coordinated Collective Bargaining, 1974-1979 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Chain Organizing, 1976-1977 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Coordinated Bargaining, 1978-1983 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- J. & J.. Ethylene Oxide, 1980-1983 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- J. & J. Corporate Strategy, 1981-1983 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- J. & J. Security Task force, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- J. & J.. Job Training, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- J. & J.. Credo. (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Legal, 1982-1984 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- J. & J.. Scott Hoyman., 1979-1981 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- J. & J.. Guillermo J. Grenier. Position Paper, 1983-1985 (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Guillermo Grenier. Funds and Foundations, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 16)
- J. & J.. Report on trip to Somerville, NJ, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 17)
- Fact Sheet, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 18)
- Employees Assistance Program (Box 82, Folder 19)
- Fact Sheet and Figures, 1977-1981 (Box 82, Folder 20)
- J. & J.. Fair Employment Practices, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 21)
- J. & J. Expenses, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 22)
- J. & J.. Dental Products Campaign, 1977-1982 (Box 82, Folder 23)
- CAT Scan Problem, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 24)
- Richard Bensinger, 1982-1983 (Box 82, Folder 25)
- Chromosome Study, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 26)
- J. & J. Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 82, Folder 27)
- J. & J. Wages and Benefits, 1982-1987 (Box 82, Folder 28)
- J. & J. South Africa Connection, 1980-1987 (Box 82, Folder 29)
- Documents and Hand Written Notes, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 30)
- J. & J.. Anti-Union letters, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 31)
- J. & J.. New Brunswick, 1982-1987 (Box 82, Folder 32)
- J. & J. Local 630- Negotiations, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 33)